<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Events Participated :: Báo Cáo Thực Tập</title>
    <link>https://Ttuandatt.github.io/AWS-Workshop/vi/4-events_participated/index.html</link>
    <description>During my internship, I participated in two events. Each one was a memorable experience that provided new, interesting, and useful knowledge, along with gifts and wonderful moments.&#xA;Event 1&#xD;Event Name: Kick-off AWS FCJ Workforce - FPTU OJT FALL 2025&#xA;Date &amp; Time: 8:30 AM Saturday, September 6, 2025&#xA;Location: 26th Floor, Bitexco Tower, 02 Hai Trieu Street, Saigon Ward, Ho Chi Minh City</description>
    <generator>Hugo</generator>
    <language>vi</language>
    <atom:link href="https://Ttuandatt.github.io/AWS-Workshop/vi/4-events_participated/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Event 1</title>
      <link>https://Ttuandatt.github.io/AWS-Workshop/vi/4-events_participated/4.1-event-1/index.html</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://Ttuandatt.github.io/AWS-Workshop/vi/4-events_participated/4.1-event-1/index.html</guid>
      <description>Summary Report: “Kick-off AWS FCJ Workforce - FPTU OJT FALL 2025”&#xD;Event Objectives&#xD;Provide information about the Internship program FCAJ Introduce support &amp; admin team Speakers&#xD;Mr. Nguyen Gia Hưng – Head of Solutions Architect - Viet Nam &amp; Cambodia | Champion Authorized Instructor Mr. Nguyen Dong Thanh Hiep – Principal Cloud Engineer | AWS First Cloud Journey | AWS Community Builders Mr. Danh Hoang Hieu Nghi – AI Engineer at Renova Cloud | 2x AWS Certified | AWS First Cloud AI Journey Key Highlights&#xD;Introduce the FCAJ program&#xD;The history of the program The reasons for why this program was established The overall aim of the program The learning materials Speakers share their stories&#xD;Networking and discussions&#xD;The workshop offered opportunities to exchange ideas with experts, peers, and business teams, enhancing the ubiquitous language between business and tech. Real-world examples reinforced the importance of the business-first approach rather than focusing solely on technology. Lessons learned&#xD;Know more about the overall view of the cloud industry How to study and work smartly in a fast pace world Be more determined with the career path Some event photos&#xD;Overall, the event provided detailed information about the program as well as give me an opportunity to make friends with passionate peers.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Event 2</title>
      <link>https://Ttuandatt.github.io/AWS-Workshop/vi/4-events_participated/4.2-event-2/index.html</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://Ttuandatt.github.io/AWS-Workshop/vi/4-events_participated/4.2-event-2/index.html</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>